Register of the National Republic records, 1918-1960
Hoover Institution Archives
- Information File B (Boxes 437-714)
  - Eisler, Gerhard [2 folders]
  - Elections (Box 539)
  - Employment
  - Espionage
  - F
  - F (Box 540-541)
  - Fabian Society (Box 542)
  - Farm - miscellaneous
  - Fascists, Italian
  - Federal Art Project
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation
  - Federal Council of Churches
  - Federal Power Commission [3 folders]
  - Federal Security Agency
  - Federal Security Agency (Box 543)
  - Federal Union
  - Federal Writers Project
  - Federation of Churches, Greater New York
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation
  - Fi
  - Fi (Box 544)
  - Field, Frederick Vanderbilt
  - Field, Marshall
  - Fields, Herman
  - Fifth Amendment
  - Fight for Freedom Committee to Defend America
  - Fl (Box 545)
  - Flag
  - Fluoridation [2 folders]
  - Flying saucers
  - Fo [2 folders]
  - Fo (Box 546)
  - Forbes, Robert G.
  - Ford Foundation
  - Ford, Henry
  - Foreign communism
    - General
    - Asia
    - C (Box 547)
    - Canada
    - Ceylon
    - Chile
    - China [2 folders]
    - China [5 folders] (Box 548)
    - Colombia (Box 549)
    - Costa Rica
    - Crete
    - Cyprus
    - Czechoslovakia
    - Denmark
    - E - F
    - England [2 folders]
    - Europe (Box 550)
    - France
    - Germany [2 folders]
    - Germany (Box 551)
    - Ghana
    - Greece
    - Guatemala
    - Hawaii
    - Holland
    - Hungary
    - Hungary [3 folders] (Box 552)
    - I - J
    - India
    - Indochina (Box 553)
    - Indonesia
    - International organizations
    - Iran
    - Italy [2 folders]
    - Japan
    - K - L (Box 554)
    - Latin America [6 folders]
    - Latin America (Box 555)
    - M - N
    - Near East
    - P - Q
    - Poland
    - Puerto Rico
    - R
    - Russia
    - Russia (Box 556-558)
    - S - T (Box 559)
    - Yugoslavia [2 folders]
    - Miscellaneous
    - Miscellaneous (Box 560-561)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 562)
  - Foreign - communist A - B [3 folders]
  - Foreign - communist A - B [3 folders] (Box 563)
  - Foreign policy
  - Foreign policy [2 folders] (Box 564)
  - Foreign trade
  - Form Research
  - Foundation for Advanced Research Analysis
  - Foundation for Economic Education
  - Foundations
    - General
    - General [4 folders] (Box 565)
    - First Word
    - Investigations
  - Fr [2 folders] (Box 566)
  - Free [2 folders]
  - Freedom House
  - Free Enterprise (Box 567)
  - Freeman, The
  - Friends of Democracy
  - Fund for the Republic [4 folders]
  - Fund for the Republic [2 folders] (Box 568)
  - G [3 folders]
  - Ga
  - Galindez, Jesus de
  - Garst, Jim (Box 569)
  - Ge
  - Gi
  - Gilbert, Dan
  - Giraud, Henri H.
  - Girl Scouts
  - Gl
  - Go [2 folders]
  - Goldfine, Bernard
  - Goldwater, Barry
  - Gookman, Benny
  - Government [3 folders] (Box 570)
  - Gr [2 folders] (Box 571)
  - Graham, Frank
  - Greenspun, Herman
  - Grunewald, Henry W.
  - Gu
  - Gw
  - H [2 folders]
  - Ha
  - Ha [4 folders] (Box 572)
  - Harriman, Averell
  - Harrington, Donald
  - H-Bomb
  - He
  - He [3 folders] (Box 573)
  - Health [3 folders]
  - Hi [2 folders] (Box 574)
  - Hiss, Alger [2 folders]
  - Hiss, Alger [4 folders] (Box 575)
  - Hitler, Adolf
  - Ho [2 folders]
  - Ho (Box 576)
  - Hoffman, Paul
  - Hoover, J. Edgar
  - House Committee on Un-American Activities (see also box 775)
  - Housing [3 folders]
  - Housing [3 folders] (Box 577)
  - Hu [2 folders]
  - Hughes, Howard
  - Hughes, Paul H.
  - Hutton, E. F.
  - Hy
  - I [5 folders] (Box 578)
  - Immigration and deportation
  - In
  - In (Box 579)
  - Indians
  - Inflation [2 folders]
  - Ingersoll
  - Institute of Applied Citizenship
  - Institute of Government [2 folders]
  - Institute of International Education (Box 580)
  - Institute for International Order
  - Institute of International Studies
  - Institute for Religious and Social Studies
  - Intelligence Digest
  - Inter
  - Internal Revenue
  - Internal Security
  - International Bank for Reconstruction
  - International Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners (Box 581)
  - International Conciliation
  - International Economic and Social Development
  - International Finance Corporation
  - International labor organizations [2 folders]
  - International organizations [3 folders]
  - International organizations [2 folders] (Box 582)
  - International Press Institute
  - Interracial Workshop
  - Isolationism
  - J [2 folders]
  - J [4 folders] (Box 583)
  - Jack, Hulan E.
  - Jamestown, Va.
  - Japan
  - Javits, Jacob
  - Jenks, M. (Box 584)
  - Jenner, William
  - Jessup, Philip
  - Jews
  - Jews (Box 585-588)
  - Justice Department [3 folders] (Box 589)
  - Juvenile delinquency
  - K
  - Ka [3 folders]
  - Kahn, Albert (Box 590)
  - Kamkin
  - Kamp, Joseph
  - Kanin, Garson
  - Karapetoff, V.
  - Karolyi, M.
  - Kasenkina, Oksana
  - Kasper, Frederick
  - Katyn massacre
  - Kaufmann, Charlotte
  - Ke
  - Keep America Free [2 folders]
  - Kefauver, Estes
  - Kennedy, John F.
  - Ki
  - Kl (Box 591)
  - Kn
  - Ko
  - Korea
  - Kr
  - Ku
  - Ku Klux Klan
  - L [4 folders] (Box 592)
  - La [3 folders]
  - La (Box 593)
  - Labor
    - General [6 folders]
    - General (Box 594-598)
    - AFL [5 folders] (Box 599)
    - AFL-CIO
    - AFL-CIO (Box 600)
    - CIO (Box 601)
    - Communism [5 folders] (Box 602)
    - Leaders
      - Beck
      - Bridges
      - Browder
      - Carey
      - Christoffel
      - De Caux
      - Doyle, Chas. A.
      - Flaxer
      - Gojack
      - Gold (Box 603)
      - Gosser
      - Hoffa
      - Killian
      - Kohler
      - McNamara
      - Markham
      - Meany
      - Quill
      - Riesel
      - Santo
      - Stellato
      - Suisi
      - Thomas
    - Politics [3 folders]
    - Right to Work [2 folders]
    - Right to Work (Box 604)
    - Union finances
    - United Auto Workers [3 folders]
    - Youth League
  - Ladejinsky, Wolf (Box 605)
  - LaGuardia
  - Lamb, Natvig
  - Lamb, Edward
  - Langer, Alfred
  - Lattimore, Owen
  - Lattimore, Owen [2 folders] (Box 606)
  - Le
  - League for Independent Political Action
  - League of Nations
  - LeBlanc Publications
  - Lehman, Herbert
  - Lend Lease
  - Lewis, Fulton
  - Lewis, John L.
  - Li
  - Li [2 folders] (Box 607)
  - Lilienthal, David
  - Lincoln, Abraham [2 folders]
  - Lo
  - Loyalty [2 folders]
  - Lu (Box 608)
  - Ly
  - M [2 folders]
  - Ma [2 folders]
  - Ma (Box 609)
  - Mc
  - MacArthur, Gen. Douglas (Box 610)
  - McCarthy, Joe
  - McCarthy, Joe (Box 611-614)
  - McCarthy, Joe [3 folders] (Box 615)
  - Mar
  - Marshall, George
  - Marxism
  - Marzani, Carl A.
  - Matusow, Harvey [2 folders] (Box 616)
  - Mauldin, Bill
  - Me
  - Meat strikes [2 folders]
  - Meat strikes [5 folders] (Box 617)
  - Meat strikes [4 folders] (Box 618)
  - Melish, John Howard
  - Mental health (Box 619)
  - Meyer
  - Mi [3 folders]
  - Mo
  - Mo [4 folders] (Box 620)
  - Money [2 folders]
  - Morgenthau, Henry (Box 621)
  - Morse, Wayne
  - Motion pictures
  - Mu [2 folders]
  - Mutual Defense Assistance
  - Mutual Security Agency [2 folders]
  - My (Box 622)
  - N [6 folders]
  - Na (Box 623-625)
  - Narcotics (Box 626)
  - National Clearing House for Youth Groups
  - National Committee to Uphold Constitutional Government
  - National Council of Churches
  - National Labor Committee Against War
  - National Peace Conference
  - National Recovery Administration
  - National Religion and Labor Foundation
  - National Sharecroppers Week
  - National Society of New England Women
  - National Union of Government
  - National Urban League
  - National Youth Assembly Against U.M.T.
  - NATO [4 folders] (Box 627)
  - Ne [3 folders] (Box 628)
  - Negro [2 folders]
  - Negro (Box 629-634)
  - Nepotism (Box 635)
  - Neuberger, Richard
  - New Deal [5 folders]
  - New School for Social Research [2 folders] (Box 636)
  - New World Club
  - Newspapers
  - New York Consumers Council
  - Ni
  - Niebuhr, Dr. Reinhold
  - Nixon, Richard [2 folders]
  - Nixon, Richard (Box 637)
  - No
  - Nu
  - O [4 folders]
  - O (Box 638)
  - Oaths
  - Obscene literature and pictures
  - Oil [2 folders]
  - Operation America
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert [2 folders]
  - Oxnam, Bishop G. B. [2 folders] (Box 639)
  - P
  - Pa [3 folders]
  - Pacifists [6 folders] (Box 640)
  - Paine, Tom
  - Panama Canal
  - Passports (Box 641)
  - Patriotic organizations
  - Pauley, Edwin
  - Pauling, Linus
  - Pe [4 folders]
  - Peace
  - Peace Now Movement
  - Pearl Harbor
  - Peck, Seymour
  - Pegler, Westbrook
  - Pelley, William D.
  - Pelley, William D. [5 folders] (Box 642)
  - People's Forum
  - People's Lobby
  - Peress case (Box 643)
  - Peurifoy, John
  - Peyser, Julius I.
  - Ph
  - Pi
  - Picture News Press, Ltd.
  - Pioneer Youth
  - Pl
  - Plecan, Theodore
  - Pm
  - Po [2 folders]
  - Po (Box 644)
  - Posters - miscellaneous
  - Post Office
  - Pr [5 folders]
  - Presidency (Box 645)
  - Press
  - Prince, I. Hudson
  - Progressives
  - Progressive Schools, Committee for Refugee Children
  - Protestant, The
  - Protestant Council, The
  - Ps
  - Psychological warfare
  - Pu [2 folders]
  - Purge Congress Campaign
  - Py
  - Q
  - R [6 folders] (Box 646)
  - R (Box 647)
  - Ra
  - Radio [3 folders]
  - Re [2 folders]
  - Reciprocal trade (Box 648)
  - Reds in government departments
  - Religion in Russia
  - Remington, William [3 folders]
  - Republican Party [3 folders]
  - Republican Party [5 folders] (Box 649)
  - Republican Party [2 folders] (Box 650)
  - Reuther, Walter [4 folders]
  - Reuther, Walter [2 folders] (Box 651)
  - Rh
  - Ri
  - Ro
  - Ro (Box 652)
  - Robeson, Paul
  - Rogue's Gallery, Red Leaders [3 folders]
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. [5 folders] (Box 653)
  - Rosenbergs Defense Group
  - Rosenberg, Julius and Ethel
  - Ru (Box 654)
  - Rural Electrification Administration [4 folders]
  - Russia (Box 655-657)
    - General
    - General [3 folders] (Box 658)
    - [3 folders], 1958
    - [4 folders], 1958 (Box 659)
    - 1959
    - 1959 (Box 660-661)
    - 1959 (Box 662)
  - S [4 folders]
  - S (Box 663)
  - Sa [2 folders]
  - Sc [2 folders]
  - Se
  - Se [2 folders] (Box 664)
  - Sedition
  - Sh [2 folders]
  - Si
  - Sl
  - Sm [3 folders] (Box 665)
  - Smith Act
  - Sno [2 folders]
  - So [2 folders]
  - So [2 folders] (Box 666)
  - Sobell, Morton
  - Soble, Myra
  - Socialism [2 folders]
  - Socialized medicine [3 folders] (Box 667)
  - Social Security
  - Social Security [4 folders] (Box 668)
  - Sockman, Ralph W.
  - Sokolsky, George
  - Sorge Spy case
  - South [2 folders] (Box 669)
  - Southeast Asia Treaty Organization
  - Southern Worker (periodical)
  - Sp [2 folders]
  - Springfield Plan, The
  - Sq
  - St [3 folders]
  - St [5 folders] (Box 670)
  - Stalin, Joseph
  - Star Spangled Banner (Box 671)
  - Stassen, Harold
  - State Department [5 folders]
  - State Department [6 folders] (Box 672)
  - States' rights (Box 673)
  - Status of Forces Treaty
  - Stevenson, Adlai [3 folders]
  - Su
  - Subversive Activities Act - State of Georgia
  - Subversive Activities Control Board
  - Subversive Activities Control Board [3 folders] (Box 674)
  - Supreme Court [3 folders]
  - Supreme Court [6 folders] (Box 675)
  - Supreme Court [2 folders] (Box 676)
  - Sw
  - Sy
  - T [3 folders]
  - T (Box 677)
  - Ta
  - Taft, Robert
  - Tamiment Institute
  - Tariffs
  - Tariffs [2 folders] (Box 678)
  - Tass News Agency
  - Tax [4 folders]
  - Tax [5 folders] (Box 679)
  - Tchou, Col. M. Thomas
  - Te
  - Te (Box 680)
  - Television [2 folders]
  - Th
  - Theater [2 folders]
  - Theater (Box 681-685)
    General note
    See also box 772
  - Theater [4 folders] (Box 686)
  - Third party [2 folders]
  - Ti
  - To (Box 687)
  - Tr [2 folders]
  - Traitors
  - Treaty
  - Tresca, Carlo
  - Trotsky, Leon
  - Truman, Harry S.
  - Truman, Harry S. [5 folders] (Box 688)
  - Trusts [5 folders] (Box 689)
  - Tu (Box 690)
  - Tydings, Millard D.
  - U [6 folders]
  - Unions (Box 691)
    - General [5 folders]
    - CIO affiliates [2 folders] (Box 692)
    - Confidential reports
    - Confidential reports [4 folders] (Box 693)
  - United Nations
    - General [2 folders]
    - General (Box 694-699)
    - General [3 folders] (Box 700)
    - Personnel [2 folders]
  - United States [3 folders] (Box 701)
  - United States Army maneuvers, Lampasa, Texas
  - Urban renewal [3 folders]
  - V
  - V [3 folders] (Box 702)
  - Veterans [3 folders]
  - Veterans [4 folders] (Box 703)
  - Voice of America
  - Voting records
  - W
  - W [3 folders] (Box 704)
  - Wa [3 folders]
  - Wa [2 folders] (Box 705)
  - Wallace, Henry
  - War Assets Administration [4 folders]
  - War Assets Administration [2 folders] (Box 706)
  - War Department [4 folders]
  - Washington, George (Box 707)
  - We [2 folders]
  - Wh [2 folders]
  - Wi
  - Wi [2 folders] (Box 708)
  - Wilson, Howard Eugene
  - Wittmer, Felix
  - Wo [2 folders]
  - Wo [2 folders] (Box 709)
  - Wolston, Ilya
  - Women
    - General [3 folders]
    - Annie Besant [3 folders] (Box 710)
    - Individuals [3 folders]
    - Individuals [2 folders] (Box 711)
    - Organizations [3 folders]
  - World Alliance of YMCA (Box 712)
  - World Council of Churches
  - World Government [3 folders]
  - World Youth and Student Festival
  - X
  - Y
  - Yalta Conference [4 folders] (Box 713)
  - Young Pioneers [2 folders]
  - Youth (Box 714)
  - Z
- Information File C (Boxes 714-768)
  Reports, printed matter, letters, and miscellany, arranged alphabetically by subject. For additional information on topics identified in this series, see Information Files A and B.
  - General (Box 714)
  - General
    National Republic and Walter Steele material.
  - Correspondence
  - Notes
    - General
    - General (Box 715)
    - A-M (Box 716)
    - N-Z
  - Abraham Lincoln Brigade (Box 717)
  - Africa
  - Agriculture (Box 718)
    - General
    - Labor
  - Albania
  - All-American Conference to Combat Communism
  - American Association of University Professors
  - American Association of University Women
  - American Civil Liberties Union
  - American Coalition of Patriotic Societies
  - American Foundation for Political Education
  - American Friends of the Soviet Union
  - American Friends Service Committee
  - American Jewish Congress
  - American Jewish League Against Communism
  - American League Against War and Fascism
  - American League for Peace and Democracy (Box 719)
  - American Legion
  - American Nazi Party
  - American Russian Institute
  - American Veterans Committee
  - Americans for Constitutional Action
  - Americans for Democratic Action
  - Anarchism
  - Antibolshevik Bloc of Nations
  - Anti-Semitism
  - Anti-Semitism (Box 720)
  - Arts (Box 721)
  - Asia
  - Atomic weapons and disarmament
  - B'nai B'rith
  - Baltic States
  - Beall, Jack
  - Browder, Earl (Box 722)
  - Budenz, Louis
  - Bulgaria
  - Carlson, John Roy
  - Central Intelligence Agency
  - Chessman, Caryl
  - China
  - China (Box 723)
  - Citizens Committee for Victory
  - Civil rights
  - Commission to Study the Organization of the Peace
  - Communism (Box 724)
    - General
    - General (Box 725)
    - International
    - United States (Box 726)
      - General
      - Arts and entertainment
      - Arts and entertainment (Box 727)
      - Education and youth
      - Education and youth (Box 728)
      - Labor
      - Labor (Box 729)
      - Military
      - Race relations
      - Religion (Box 730)
  - Communist League (Box 731)
  - Communist Party, U.S.A.
  - Condon, Edward U.
  - Crouch, Paul
  - Conservative organizations (Box 732)
  - Constitutional Educational League, Inc. (Joseph Kamp) (Box 733)
  - Coughlin, Charles E.
  - Crime and criminals
  - Cyprus
  - Czechoslovakia
  - Daily Worker
  - Daughters of the American Revolution
  - Davies, John Paton
  - De Courcy, Kenneth
  - Defenders of the American Constitution
  - Defense
  - Defense (Box 734)
  - Dell, Floyd
  - Dewey, John
  - Dilling, Elizabeth
  - Discrimination and race relations
    - General
    - General (Box 735)
    - General (Box 736)
    - Little Rock, Arkansas
  - DuBois, W.E.B.
  - Economics
  - Economics (Box 737)
  - Education (Box 738)
  - Einstein, Albert
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
  - Eisler, Gerhart
  - Espionage (Box 739)
  - Europe
  - Europe, Eastern
  - Fascism - United States
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation
  - Federated Council for Americanism (Box 740)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation
  - Fluoridation
  - Flynn, John
  - Foreign Policy Association
  - Foster, William Z.
  - Fraina, Louis (Lewis Corey)
  - France
  - Foundation for Economic Education
  - Friends Committee on National Legislation
  - Friends of Democracy
  - Friends of Fighters for Russian Freedom
  - Fund for the Republic
  - Germany
  - Great Britain
  - Greece (Box 741)
  - Highlander Folk School
  - Hiss, Alger
  - History
  - Housing
  - Human rights
  - Hungary
  - Immigration (Box 742)
  - India
  - Indonesia
  - Intellectuals
  - International Press Correspondence
  - International programs
  - Isolationism
  - Italy (Box 743)
  - Japan
  - Jefferson School of Social Sciences
  - Jessup, Philip
  - Jewish National Fund
  - Jews and Jewish organizations
  - Kohlberg, Alfred (Box 744)
  - Korea
  - Kregeloh, Hubert
  - Krivitsky, Walter
  - Labor
  - Labor (Box 745)
  - Labor (Box 746)
  - Labor (Box 747)
  - Latin America (Box 748)
  - Lattimore, Owen
  - League for Industrial Democracy
  - League of Women Voters
  - Liberal organizations
    - General
    - General (Box 749)
    - Information and propaganda
  - Liberalism
  - Life Lines
  - Lincoln, Abraham
  - Loyalty-security program
  - Loyalty-security program (Box 750)
  - Mandel, Ben
  - McCarthy, Joseph
  - Marcantonio, Vito
  - Media
  - Medicine and health
  - Medicine and health (Box 751)
  - Middle East
  - Middle East (Box 752)
  - Minute Women of the U.S.A.
  - Miscellany
  - Moral Re-Armament Assembly (Box 753)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People
  - National Committee for an Effective Congress
  - National Council for American Education
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship
  - National Lawyers Guild
  - Native Americans
  - Natural resources and energy
  - Nelson, Steve (Box 754)
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold
  - Nixon, Richard
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert
  - Pacifism
  - Pakistan
  - Pauling, Linus
  - Pearson, Drew
  - Philbrick, Herbert
  - People's World
  - Perlo, Victor
  - Philippines
  - Poland
  - Post War World Council
  - Propaganda and psychological warfare
  - Psychology and mental health
  - Refugees
  - Religion (Box 755)
  - Religion and politics
  - Rieve, Emil
  - Riskin, Ben
  - Rockefeller Family
  - Romania
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. and Eleanor
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. and Eleanor (Box 756)
    - Russia
    - General
    - General (Box 757)
    - General (Box 758)
    - Foreign relations
  - Scandinavia
  - Science and space (Box 759)
  - Scientific and Cultural Conference for World Peace, 1949
  - Service Bureau for Intercultural Education
  - Service, John S.
  - Smith, Gerald L. K.
  - Socialism
  - Socialist Labor Party
  - Socialist Workers Party
  - Social Security and welfare
  - Spain
  - Steel, Johannes
  - Stevenson, Adlai
  - Taiwan (Box 760)
  - Trade
  - Transportation
  - Trumbo, Dalton
  - Union for Democratic Action
  - United Nations
  - United Nations (Box 761)
  - United States
    - Foreign relations
      - General
      - General (Box 762)
      - Foreign aid
      - Organizations (Box 763)
      - Russia
    - Politics and government (Box 764)
    - Politics and government (Box 765)
  - United States. Congress
  - United States. Congress (Box 766)
  - United States. State Department
  - United States. Supreme Court
  - Urban planning
  - Veterans
  - Vietnam (Box 767)
  - Wallace, Henry
  - Weyl, Nathaniel
  - White, Harry Dexter
  - Winrod, Gerald
  - Women
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom
  - World Court
  - World government
  - World War II (Box 768)
  - Yugoslavia
- Hazel Huffman Office Files, circa 1938-1949 (Boxes 769-772)
  Correspondence, notes lists, reports, and printed matter relating to investigations undertaken by Huffman. Arranged alphabetically by subject of investigation. See also: Federal Theater, boxes 680-686.
  - General (Box 769)
    Correspondence, notes, and lists.
  - General (Box 770)
  - Coast Guard (Box 771)
  - Federal Security Administration
  - Fort Leavenworth Prison Riot
  - Office of War Information
  - War Assets Administration
  - War Assets Administration (Box 772)
    See also boxes 680-686
  - Works Progress Administration, Federal Theatre Project
- Office File of Executive Director (Walter S. Steele), 1929-1960 (Boxes 773-784)
  Catalogue, indices, lettergrams, drafts of articles, notes, report, survey, and testimony, arranged as listed.
  - Catalogue of organizations and their leadership [5 folders] (Box 773)
  - Index to Dies Committee publications [3 folders] (Box 774)
  - Index to Dies Committee publications (Box 775)
  - Index to House Committee on Un-American Activities publications [3 folders], 1945-1949
  - Lettergrams No. 14-274 (duplicate copies, see also box 404) [3 folders] (Box 776)
  - Manuscript drafts of various articles for National Republic [2 folders]
  - Manuscript drafts of various articles for National Republic [6 folders] (Box 777)
  - Manuscript drafts of various articles for National Republic [2 folders] (Box 778)
  - Notes [4 folders] (Box 779-782)
  - Notes [2 folders] (Box 783)
  - Report on communism in Shanks Village, N.Y.
  - Survey concerning foundations and Communist causes [not in folder]
  - Testimony of Walter S. Steele before House Committee on Un-American Activities [4 folders]
  - Testimony of Walter S. Steele before House Committee on Un-American Activities [4 folders] (Box 784)
- Card Index to Photos Used in National Republic Magazine (Box 815-817)
  See UNFILMED MATERIAL, Photo File, boxes 785-814, for the photos themselves.
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1925-1939 (Boxes 818-823)
  Letters to Walter Steele, publisher of the National Republic. Also includes a preliminary guide to the collection.
  - Preliminary guide and shipping list to the collection prepared by the National Republic magazine. (Box 818-823)
- UNFILMED MATERIAL
- Printed Matter (Boxes 1-37)
  Some specific printed matter from the collection was not microfilmed (aside from the title pages). These items are now housed in the physical boxes 1-37 (different from the boxes 1-37 listed in the microfilmed material section), with the box numbers they originally came from listed below.
  - 34-150 (Box 1)
  - 151-154 (Box 2)
  - 154-155 (Box 3)
  - 155-186 (Box 4)
  - 187-202 (Box 5)
  - 203-221 (Box 6)
  - 222-252 (Box 7)
  - 253-260 (Box 8)
  - 261-270 (Box 9)
  - 272-295 (Box 10)
  - 297-315 (Box 11)
  - 316-355 (Box 12)
  - 357-364 (Box 13)
  - 366-370 (Box 14)
  - 372-394 (Box 15)
  - 395-398, 416-422 (Box 16)
  - 444-451 (Box 17)
  - 452-458 (Box 18)
  - 459-467 (Box 19)
  - 468-483 (Box 20)
  - 484-503 (Box 21)
  - 504-515 (Box 22)
  - 515-523 (Box 23)
  - 524-543 (Box 24)
  - 544-565 (Box 25)
  - 566-596 (Box 26)
  - 597-620 (Box 27)
  - 621-643 (Box 28)
  - 645-658 (Box 29)
  - 660-670 (Box 30)
  - 671-699 (Box 31)
  - 700-717 (Box 32)
  - 718-725 (Box 33)
  - 726-739 (Box 34)
  - 740-751 (Box 35)
  - 752-761 (Box 36)
  - 762-770, legal size material (Box 37)
- Communist Party Pamphlet File, 1920-1956 (Boxes 407-415)
  Pamphlets published by communist organizations, arranged alphabetically by last name of author. Box 407 contains an index listing pamphlets alphabetically by subject.
  - Index (by subject) (Box 407)
  - Abolin, A. "The October Revolution and the Trade Unions,", 1933
  - Adoratsky, V. "The History of the Communist Manifesto,", 1938
  - Afonin, A. "Komsomol,", 1934
  - Allan, William. "Your House on Alger Street,", undated